A Guide to the Rockefeller University records, Special Events and Activities, Rockefeller University Centennial FA894
Rockefeller Archive Center
Rockefeller University records, Special Events and Activities, Rockefeller University Centennial
1999-2002
Rockefeller Archive Center
Rockefeller University
Rockefeller Institute for Medical Research
FA894
1 Cubic Feet
2 boxes.
Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements note
Materials requiring specialized equipment for access (film, audio, video, slides) may be closed to research dependent on availability of the applicable equipment
Brittle or damaged items, or materials otherwise in need of preservation care, may be closed to researchers at the discretion of the RAC Head of Archival Services/Head of Reference.
File Plan note
Former Classification: I 600-25
Conditions Governing Access
Collection is open for scholarly research, with select materials restricted as noted.
China; Medical care; Medical research; Cell and biomolecular sciences; Biology -- Research; Medical sciences; Medicine, Preventive; Vivisection; DNA; Genetics; MacLeod, Colin M. (Colin Munro); Rockefeller University; McCarty, Maclyn; Rockefeller Institute for Medical Research; Avery, Oswald Theodore; Seitz, Frederick
- "The Emergence of Modern Philanthropy, The Rockefeller Story" - Video of Program 7 December 1999, 1999 December 7; Video (Box 1, Folder 1)
  Conditions Governing Access
  RAC is unable to provide access to obsolete media. When feasible, a digital surrogate may be created via special order. All applicable charges will apply. See RAC Head of Archival Services or RAC Head of Digital Programs for details.
- Centennial Exhibitions - brochure 2000 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- "Creating a Tradition of Biomedical Research" - RU Centennial History Conference 2000 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- "At the Crossroads of Science" - Centennial Lecture on Science and Society, 2000 November 13 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- "Philanthropy in a Global Century" - The Rockefeller University Council - program, 2000 December 5 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Centennial Convocation, 2001 June (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Centennial Employee Picnic, 2001 June 22 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Rockefeller University Centennial Calendar Academic Year 2001 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- "Discovering the Rockefeller University" - Newsletter (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Centennial Film - Final Version November 2001, 2001 November; VHS video cassette (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Centennial Symposium - Celebration of Excellence in Neuroscience, 2001 October 23-24 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Centennial Symposium - From Gene to Organism, 2002 February 28-March 1 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- RU Centennial History Conference, 2000 November; 9 VHS cassettes of meeting (Box 2)
- "Creating a Tradition of Biomedical Research" November 2000, 2000 November; Oversize.; Poster on foam core
  Separated Materials
  Relocated to map case.
  Due to the oversize nature and potential brittle condition of the contents of this collection, special arrangements may be required in order to view materials. Individual items may be restricted due to preservation concerns.